Chase Brown

Software Engineer

Grand Junction CO cabrown.business@gmail.com

Objective

I am an innovative Computer Scientist who learns quickly and embraces challenges. I seek to obtain a full-time opportunity that will allow me to use/expand my knowledge of software engineering, cybersecurity, and new technologies. I hope to learn, grow, and experience a myriad of new things.

Skills

Programming in Python, C/C++, JavaScript, React, Intel/ARM x86 Assembly, SQL, NoSQL Experience planning, analyzing, designing, implementing, testing, and maintaining large scale programs.

Knowledgeable in Linux, Windows, Git/GitHub, and AWS

Experience in a small startup-style environment, Agile/Scrum, and working beyond the job title.

Experience

Walker Products Inc., Grand Junction CO - Software Engineer

July 2019 - PRESENT

- Design, develop, manage, and maintain automotive testing software using Python, C++, and SQL from scratch
- Develop compact, secure code for microcontrollers using C/C++
- Integrate and deploy software components into a fully functional hardware test system using Git
- Produce specifications and determine operational feasibility of given hardware
- Maintained, managed, and operated 3D printers and accompanying software
- Communicate and collaborate among fellow engineers and production employees to attain a common goal

NASA Colorado Space Grant Consortium, Grand Junction CO - Intern

June 2019 - July 2019

- Build and maintain rapid prototyping machines such as 3D printers, CNC machines, and CO2 laser cutters
- Assist in development of JavaScript program to interact with hardware

Education

Colorado Mesa University, Grand Junction CO - Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

2018 - 2021

Graduated Magna Cum Laude • 3.91 GPA • Minor in Cybersecurity

Certifications

Professional Certification in Cybersecurity - Colorado Mesa University 2021

Projects

MAF Sensor Test Stand

Developed large-scale program and hardware to interact with physical test-stand to automatically test automotive sensor functionality

Used Python, SQL, TKinter, Matplotlib, and many other libraries

Successfully implemented solution that more than doubled production numbers, while reducing possibility for human error and gathering more accurate test data

Excel to SQL Transfer

Designed, tested and delivered program to analyze thousands of excel spreadsheets and transfer relevant data to SQL database.

Used Python, Sqlite, Pandas

Successfully analyzed and transferred 100% of data to database before deadline

React Web Page

Designed and deployed a react web page for the game Breakout. Included score tracking and user login system

Used React and MongoDB

Successfully delivered the final project to the client on time

Al Iris Classification

Create and analyze multiple models for predicting iris species given the 4 features using multiple machine-learning models including K Neighbors Classifier and Support Vector Classification.

Uses Python, SKLearn, Keras.

Achieved 100% accuracy in species identification.